<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<books>
  <book ID="Meph_ModJam2024_Pet02_Story" Title="{{W|Acid Released}}">
    <page>
The tartbeard curled up in his box. It was a special box. It wasn't like the other cages. He could see out of it but he couldn't escape it. It was sealed too tight. And it was made out of something that didn't sizzle when he spat at it. He hated this box. The others hated their cages too. He could see them, almost hear them, clawing at the bars. He tried to spit on the bars, sizzle them down so they could escape, but the walls of the box got in the way. He would hiss at the Bad People whenever they picked up his box. He was afraid, but he hoped they would set him free. They never did. They put him on a table, and there were lots of people. Noise. Too loud. Too many people and nowhere to hide. So many people, he couldn't see the others. He heard their cries, muffled through the box. His acid rose in anger and he spat, but the box got in the way. He saw one of his friends taken away, wheeled away in their cage. A bird. They flapped and screamed, then the people got in the way and he couldn't see them anymore. He never saw them again.

His stomach grumbled. Once a day, a Bad Person would open his box and throw a strip of meat in. He would spit at the Bad Person, but they wore something over their hands and face that made his acid not do anything. The Bad Person would laugh, and close the box, and kick it. The meat was tough. It took a lot of spitting before it was chewable. It was never enough.

One day, a stranger approached the Bad People. They talked for a while. Then the Bad People started shouting. Loud enough that the others started shouting, too. Then, the stranger did something, and a cloud of gas washed over the Bad People. Looked just like mama when she was angry. There were loud bangs. Fear. He hissed and spat, scrabbled at the walls of the box. He tipped it over and he tumbled down. The box bounced. Didn't break. Anger. Fear. Couldn't see anything through the acid. His or the stranger's.

Things went quiet. Couldn't hear anything besides the others. But they were going quiet. Getting quieter. Until there was silence. Fear. Don't take them away. Save them. Couldn't get out. Claws didn't work against the box.
Then a shadow fell over the box. Picked it up. Righted it. Opened it. He whipped around and spat, hissing as bravely as he could.
The stranger chuckled. 'Whoa, there.' They didn't seem to worried about his acid. They had a cloth, covering their face. It sizzled and smoked from where his acid splashed it. They pulled the cloth down and exhaled, and a cloud of acid billowed over the tartbeard. It tingled where it touched his scales. Acidic. Familiar. 'See?' The stranger said. 'I'm just like you. Tch... Look at you. Practically still a baby. Bastards. They had it coming.' The stranger beckoned. The box was open. 'Come on out, little fella. I daresay you've had enough of that thing to last you a lifetime.'
The tartbeard looked around crawled out, cautiously. Felt real earth under his feet for the first time in a long time. Looked around. Bodies. Blood. Empty cart. Empty cages.
The others, escaping into the distance. Free...
'Would you like to come with me?'
The tartbeard looked up at the Stranger. Their face was scarred. Skin burned and gnarled like a withered tree. They smiled, cracking their cheeks like sunburnt soil, reached down a hand to the tartbeard. He sniffed it. Butted his head against it. The Stranger flipped his hand over and tickled the tartbeard under his chin, making him squeak.
'Ha. I'll take that as a yes, then. Alright. You'll need a name...
'Hm. How about Stubble?'
    </page>
  </book>
</books>
