<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<!--Templates -->

<books>
	<book ID="Aric Billy Sass" Title="Aric Billy Sass">
		<page>It's a baaaad day to mess with us.</page>
		<page>Seen any trolls lately? Hate trolls.</page>
		<page>They say trolls know everything, but really it's only like 4 things. </page>
		<page>You know, I've seen some nice horns, but mine are just different, you know?</page>
		<page>BAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA!</page>
		<page>A snapjaw told me I was the horniest goat he'd ever met. I think I'm just friendly.</page>
		<page>Never fight I troll in it's healing pool. Take it to a bridge instead.</page>
		<page>A troll tried to eat me once. But I used my superior intellect to confuse it, then my big brother killed him.</page>
		<page>Got any carrots?</page>
		<page>Got any hay?</page>
		<page>Got any trollflesh?</page>
		<page>I've heard it said I'm the greatest. Wouldn't you agree?</page>
		<page>You know, goatfolk eating humans is just the circle of life. Humans eat goats, goatfolk eat humans, goats eat goatfolk. Wait. Forget I said that.</page>
		<page>You know, not enough goats braid their beards, on account of the hooves. Look good though.</page>
		<page>Have you ever been to the purple place? You can't even eat the grass, your teeth go right through like nothing's there.</page>
		<page>I hate the desert. Issachar don't even have any blood to drink. Salt and sun indeed.</page>
		<page>I love the jungle. So much delicious.... food.</page>
		<page>Humans can't walk on mountains? But it's really easy? Just another way we're superior I suppose</page>
		<page>I never really saw the point of oppposable thumbs. The point of my horns is enough for me.</page>
		<page>Now the salt marsh, that's a good place to be. Lots of places for a good goat to live his best life.</page>
		<page>The flower fields are pretty, and I love exploding plants as much as the next goat, but the last one singed my beard. Took weeks to grow back.</page>
		<page>You know some people think the banana men were trees? Have they ever even seen a tree?</page>
		<page>Have you ever seen a troll try to swim? They can't. It's great.</page>
		<page> I've always wondered why they call it an Issachar Rifle. Goats use them too you know. It should be called a Goat Gun.</page>
	 </book>
	  
	  <book ID="Aric The Story of a Great Goat" Title="The Story of a Great Goat">
		
		<page>The Troll Kings once roamed the surface of Qud, claiming ownership of every bridge over the River Svy, exacting their terrible toll, or forcing would be crossers to contend with the Madpoles. Goats, on the other hand are small in Qud, their horns are believed to be inferior to those of creatures such a Gnu and Chameleons.  The least of all creatures, some say! But Big Billy, one of three brother goats, broke this mould. His horns were long and sharp, and he was far stronger than any of his kin. And so it was that Big Billy decided to take his brothers to the great feeding lands of the jungle. But the young Billies were afraid, for while their brother was great and strong, trolls are so very terrible. Thus a plan was hatched, and Billy and his younger brother went ahead and distracted the troll. As he threatened to eat them, and demanded their water, Big Billy approached from behind, threw him into the river and he was eaten by madpoles. Trolls have feared bridges ever since, and now retreat into the bowels of the earth, or so Billy says.  </page>
		
	  </book>
</books>	  